It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like the wind, jump high.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going on the stage.
Let's do it again.
You know what I mean, baby!
Know what you're making my dream? Time to?
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the crazy.
I know there are no rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wild.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you.
Only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
But if you don't want to
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like the wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you cannot achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going. Rolling.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your wife that I
want, but you're where it was.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life,
shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong. Just
that you gotta keep your best.
Let's keep on going. I'm not dead.
You make my day every day.
Are you crazy?
You're gonna pay!
This voice is a real sensitive issue!
Fuck it off or he's gonna
flip out and kill us too!
Brace yourselves, because we're about to
get punched by a whole freaking castle!
I can feel that there's trouble looming.
Admiral, a monster is coming!
We have to take cover!
Luffy, you really gotta stop
screwing with every enemy!
See, it's so hard not to crack up, huh?
Damn, you too.
This ain't gonna be pretty!
Where are we now?
Like I'd know.
Even further from the
palace, thanks to you.
Damn it.
That stone bastard's something else.
Never thought we'd see someone
bigger than oars, but here we are.
How am I supposed to even fight
something that size, Straw Hat?
Pirate hunter Zoro I
presume and you Trafalgar
You disgusting worst generation scoundrel,
why do you steal all the glory from me?
Stop yelling!
Got to beef with my crewmate or something?
I'm not in your crew!
Let me guess, you still
got a grudge against us!
You're wrong.
I shall no longer be a
threat to the Straw Hats.
Huh?
Because your brave crewmate, God Usopp,
selflessly saved me from
a life of doom and gloom.
Usopp did that? That's right.
I won't forget his valiant deed.
He boldly risked everything in order
to spare the lives of hundreds.
Ha!
Chucks, it's nice to hear
you compliment my crew!
Oh, right.
Trafalgar, I believe this is yours.
I happened upon it
outside of the Coliseum.
I'm sure you've been longing for it.
Lend me your head a second.
Get away from me!
I don't trust you!
Hmph.
Like I'd waste any more time on
you, I have a schedule to maintain.
Aren't you going to
inquire why I'm so busy?
I'm good.
I have decided to repay my debt to your
crew by seizing the head of Doflamingo.
The hell?
Seek shelter in dirt or whatever you do.
I shall handle these matters as tribute.
Yeah, no thanks.
I'm going to do it myself.
I already decided this is how I'm going
to pay back Rebecca for buying me lunch.
You're going head to head
with a warlord over some food?
I won't fall for it.
How dare you lie to my face?
You're just trying to take out Doflamingo
for the fame and riches that follow.
That sounds like you, actually.
Just ponder it a moment.
He who brings down the
dastardly ghost flamingo will
make headlines ensuring the
whole world turns their head!
Imagine the crowds clamoring to meet you!
Mr.
Superstar Playboy extraordinaire!
Just Superstar will suffice.
No need to be formal.
What is it?
Excuse me, sir.
What's your opinion regarding
piracy in recent years?
Oh, are you still there?
I'm having trouble seeing!
Lord Cavendish, sir?
What's the problem?
I'm standing here in front of you.
You're shining so bright we can't see you.
Can you turn down your aura?
Is it too intense for you?
I apologize, but I cannot
suppress my brilliance.
Oh, he really is a superstar.
All right.
Time to go.
Please feel free to bask
in my glory. Take it in.
Take it all in.
What about here?
Keep searching for Straw Hat's body.
After a punch like that, he might
have been crushed to smithereens.
Perhaps he got away.
Find him!
I need to know if the
little maggot's still alive!
I'll squash you flat
before you get to Dorry!
There you are, Straw Hat!
Get out of my way! Move! Move!
You heard me go!
I know that guy!
Grandson of God, wait for me!
We've been looking for you, rubber boy!
Stay!
Stay right there!
Ugh, not so!
We're coming for you!
We should go! Run!
What's getting into you?
But we told him to wait!
You've got more company?
He's away already!
Stop all of you!
Head on!
Is there something wrong with
your hearing, grandson of Garp?
Just hear this old man out for a moment.
I wanted to let you know I've forgiven
the grudge I held against your family.
What? You did?
We're here for one thing, and that's to
eliminate Doflamingo's immoral business.
We don't care about the money.
A puny bounty like that
is mere change for us.
I must thank you and your friend for the
brave god Usopp rescued
me in my darkest hour.
Usopp did that?
Decided to repay my debt
to the Straw Hats by
obliterating Doflamingo and his
wicked monarchy. Huh? You two?
The only guy who's kicking his ass is me.
The nerve of you!
Are you rejecting my generous favor?
Straw Hat, I was searching for you.
I say we buried a hatchet between us.
I swear as a proud warrior of Elbath,
I'll slay Doflamingo!
but guard Usopp.
We of the Prodent's kingdom have
long owed King Rick an enormous debt.
I'll bring down Doflamingo
with my own two fists.
Yes, his majesty's right.
We don't want the bounty, not this time.
Stand down.
We will be the ones who kill that bastard.
We shall never forget that beacon of
light, who freed us from our torment.
Let us repay his valor. Wait!
I won't let you do this without me!
Destruction's my specialty!
You can leave the execution to me.
Back off!
I'll be the one to take his life
You really attract some oddballs, huh?
You'd be a fool to forget me.
Great, Big Mouth found us again.
Hey, what if we do it this way?
Us two will handle killing Doflamingo
While you guys watch our backs, sound okay?
Absolutely not!
I'm going to kill Go Flamingo!
Forget it.
There are way too many egos involved.
Come on, guys.
Alright, I'm making
the call, so listen up!
If anyone here's gonna kick his ass like
it needs to be kicked, it's gonna be me!
What did you say?
You're getting this favor
returned one way or another.
If you save someone's life,
you better learn to accept their
kindness or else, you moron!
That's right! Guilty!
Attention!
My pride!
The team!
Ah, savior!
The spear!
So that's where they were!
Hey, you think we could get in on this?
Splitting up all those
bounties could go a long way!
Wait a sec.
Don't they look kind of familiar to you?
They were toys at the dock just like us.
Those shapeless cowards, how dare they?
Let's get that bounty!
You ungrateful swine!
I'll see you in hell!
Let's go. Yeah.
It's Lucy!
A cow?
Got an idea.
It can't be.
Oh, bull!
Go! Go!
I've located the Straw Hats!
Look, Master Pika!
They came right to us!
Don't let them get away!
They're riding a bull!
I've got eyes on three.
Wait, I mean, four, five, six, seven!
Wait, Straw Hat!
I said get lost!
He brought an army?
Where did they come from?
I said I've got this!
You all can stand down!
That's enough!
I won't hesitate to slice you all
into pieces if you get in my way!
Wrong!
That would be my privilege. No, mine!
How did he get so many
allies on such short notice?
How should I know?
Aren't those some of the
competitors from the Coliseum?
I'll crush as many of you as it takes.
Now die!
Here we go.
Drill Dragon!
Although I'm not fully charged up
yet, I got a light one for you.
King Punch!
Nailed!
Here I go!
They shattered his arm!
We can consider this our practice round
for when we finally get to Doflamingo.
right?
Oh, Moose off!
I said I got it!
Shut up!
You ungrateful savior!
I don't need your help!
I hope that's done.
That serves you right,
you big whiny brood.
That was close!
Yeah, giddy up!
Go, Moosey! Easy, boy.
We're all counting on you.
Hey, I told you, you're not invited.
Get off of Moosey!
Oh, please reconsider.
We're already here.
Yeah, Straw Hat, let us in on the fun.
Come on, Moosey, tell him.
Where is the justice
one, you little bastard?
Hey, don't let them get through.
They're heading straight for the palace.
Let me jump in.
Giddy-o, the champion fighter!
Straw Hat's getting away.
Forget about me already?
Destruction King!
Better send in some big guns,
otherwise there's no stopping me!
These guys are crazy!
Commodore Olympus!
If I were you, I'd get
out of my way, Commodore!
Shoot him!
Blade of Beauty, Swan Lake!
there's trouble on the way.
he's gonna throw another one.
not again?
it's round two.
i wouldn't do it.
you obviously don't know
what you're dealing with.
here his arms grow back even
if you break him ten times.
stop wasting energy.
what are you?
suggest we do?
i say we flee.
you're a paid professional.
you really got nothing else.
retreating is a valid strategy.
you want to live?
don't you?
running at him head on is not viable.
let's take a detour.
how do we get through him?
we won't make it to the
palace at this rate.
Where did Straw Hat run off to, huh?
I lost sight of him.
He may have been pulverized.
There he is!
Yee-haw!
Good boy!
Go, go, go!
He's going up there!
Let's go!
Mercy!
No way!
He's gone crazy!
He can't upstage me!
Didn't expect that.
Let's ride to the palace in style!
Yeah!
Pastor Moosey, go!
Hey.
Yes?
This is my ball, stowaways! So? Get off!
You're weighing Moosey down!
Oh right, excuse us for not
introducing ourselves sooner.
My name is Jeet and the
big fellow behind me is?
Abdulla, hey!
I didn't ask.
Whoa, whoa!
There you are!
He looks pissed!
I won't let you get near Dolphy!
His arm's growing back.
Mr. Strawhead!
Oh, God!
Grizzly Madness!
Incredible!
His head broke!
Or Pika!
Oh, yeah!
We never doubted you, Straw Hat!
We knew you should do it!
All right!
Luffy!
I don't think you should be
celebrating just yet, sorry!
He's still out there!
The head you shattered
was just a stone decoy!
So that means Squeaky got away?
Where is he?
He's around here?
His real body's up ahead.
Uh, there's a guy inside the big rock guy?
This is the first time we're
actually seeing him in the flesh.
He's got a huge katana.
It's not too late to turn around.
You ever say this too, Moosey?
No!
We're gonna die!
Hey!
Huh? Huh?
The bull can fly?
Hmm?
That voice still gets me!
Mr. Hat!
Here he comes again!
Catch you later!
What the?
Okay, I got this!
Ah, so cool!
How dare you!
God, that's such bad-ass friends!
Zoro, be careful!
I'm gonna go give Mingo
the beating he deserves!
You go get him, Captain.
I have a score to settle! Move!
You'll have to fight me first.
He has better things to do than
tangle with a pebble like you.
Deal with it, Soprano Man.
I'm all that you've got.
That monster stopped dead in its
tracks! Is he dead? Doubt it.
That's far too convenient.
Regardless, it seems like those annoying
punches of his have ceased for the moment.
So let's strike while we can!
The flamingos shall die by
my hand! No mine! No mine!
You got this, Brook!
Let's keep it up! Yeah!
Go, Mozzarella!
Nice work!
Moosey is my wife!
If you want one, then get
off and find your own!
You're such a kidder!
We love you, Straw Hat!
Hey Straw Hat, I realize we have
no choice but to kill do flamingo.
Now that's fine.
I'm ready.
I know that's not the plan.
I suggested before.
I thought we could get away
with a less direct approach.
But to be perfectly honest with you, I
want to make him suffer with my own hands!
I won't let him defeat me again.
It was a person I cared for deeply.
And Doflamigo killed him.
His name was Corazon.
He was a former top executive
in the Don Quixote family.
The Doflamingo killed his own friend?
Corazon was the man who saved my life.
But the Doflamingo, he was more than
just a member of the Don Quixote family.
He was his younger brother.